Guide to the Samuel Shaffer papers, 1948-1982 MS2091
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Chronological files, 1948-1976; MS2091 Series 1; 17 Linear feet
  - Chronological files, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid] Nation (Bernstein) from Shaffer (6-28)(Congress Week) Correction (6/29/63)(N27 New Congress) Newsmakers from Shaffer (July 3)(Senate clash; between Dirksen and Douglas); Newsmakers from Shaffer (7-11)(Humphrey guotes); Nation (Goldman) from Shaffer (civil rights) Goldwater (7/12) Rockefeller; Biz (Martz) from Shaffer (7-12)(Railroad strike threat) Borchgrave from Shaffer (7-12)(Joint press conference of Dirksen and Halleck); Correction (7/13/63)(Feather in his cap) Correction (7/20/63)(N23 New Republican); Nation (Underhill) from Shaffer (7-18)(The Rockefeller-; Goldwater fight) Civil rights (7/25) Test ban treaty-JFK breakfast (7/25)
  - Chronological files, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    [from original finding aid] Goldwater postdated Goldwater checks; Biz Trends; Russell cover; Russall Cover file (7-22); Lester Bernstein from Shaffer (8/2)(contacts for; Birchite story); Congress Week; Correction (8/3/63) (Nl 8 Congress); Foreign from Shaffer (Domestic political consequences of Vietnam situation); Add to nuclear test ban story; Nuclear test ban (9-6-63 ); Nation from Shaffer (closed-door testimony); Newsmakers from Shaffer (9-5) (Johnson's Scandinavian trip)
  - Chronological files, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    [from original finding aid] The Church Amendment; Transition from Shaffer (Clair Engle); The Testban debate (9-13); Rocky-Goldwater query; Nation from Shaffer (if can't use this tax story, please refer to Peri; congressional Reform; Newsmakers from Shaffer (9-11) (LBJ Scandinavian tour); Add to Congress and wheat sale story (9-16-63); Add Wheat Red Trade story; Congress and the Canadian Wheat Deal (9-19); Congressional response to Birmingham; Test Ban Treaty; The Goldwater story (9/(26)
  - Chronological files, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    [from original finding aid] Congress-taxes or civil rights; Nation (Bernstein) from Shaffer (Denison Kitchel); Nation from Shaffer (9/28); Newsmakers from Shaffer (9/26/63 ) (Candid Camera Show); Bernstein from Shaffer ( 10-1 ) (Goldwater ); Congress-- - ( 10-4); Congress and the Wheat Deal; Add Wheat miscellaneous; Nation (Greene) from Shaffer (Jan 6, 1965)(Long and Ford) Foreign Nation from Shaffer(1/11/65)(Congress and Vietnam; Crisis ); Congress Week (1/12/65) Add to Congress File (1/12/65) Outlook on Presidential proposals Strom Thurmond Newsmakers(Roder) from Shaffer (11/5/65)(Dirksen and; marigolds) Add to Burch file (1/14/65); Life and Leisure from Shaffer (Xmas Cards)(Goldwater)
  - Chronological files, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Chronological files, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Chronological files, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Chronological files, 01/01/1965-01/15/1965 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Chronological files, 01/16/1965-01/31/1965 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] Vietnam Debate; Add to Vietnam story; Further add on Vietnam; Government snooping; Inaugural speech reaction; Add to file on Inaugural speech reacrion; Correction (1/23/65)(N12 New Snooping); The New York Mayorality (with Lindsay on Lindsay); Vietnam debate; Books from Shaffer (Poetry Consultant); Add Poetry Consultant Memo; Congress-To Follow Lindsay file on Nasser hassle
  - Chronological files, 02/1965 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Newsmakers (Roeder) from Shaffer (2/3/65)(Guest); Add to Congress Roundup; Congress Roundup; Correction (2/6/65)(N14 Violin); Nation (Terry Slain) frmm Shaffer (2/6/65)(N14 Violin); To Ed Diamond from Shaffer (Wash)(2/11/65)(Senate; Internal Security); Foreign (Christopher) from Shaffer (2-12)(Vietnam); Newsmakers Roeder from Shaffer (Powell's) Correction (2/27/65)(N19 Congress); Congress Correction (2/27/65)(N17 Congress)
  - Chronological files, 03/01/1965-03/099/1965 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Nation (Iselin) from Shaffer (March 4,1965)(Congressional outlook on Presidential message); Vietnam and Congress/Violin Bobby Kennedy Dirksen; Newsmakers from Shaffer Selma; Selma Washington Index,(March 8-13, 1965); No.3 3/9/65 To: Foreign/Nation/Periscope from; Norman (McNamara Backgrounder) No.l 3/9/65; Query Desk from Washington/Bradlee (Washington Bureau schedule)
  - Chronological files, 03/10/1965-03/11/1965 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] No.5 3/10/65 To Sciencs, Hubbard from Simmons; (Penny) No.20 3/10/65 Newsmakers (Roeder) from Milligan; (Lady Bird Johnson-Washington Beautification) No.3 3/11/65 Newsmakers, Roeder from Van Voorst; (Haiti: Papa Doc Duvalier); No.20 3/11/65 Foreign from Volkov (Leadall) No.29 3/11/65 Ev Martin, Foreign from Weintal; (Soviet-Vietnam); No.14 3/11/65 Nation from Shaffer (Goldwater); Nation 3/11/65 from Shaffer (Goldwater) No.23 3/11/65 Nation/Goldman from Gray (Selma) No.4 3/11/65 Von Wettburg from Crawford; (One Man, One Vote?)
  - Chronological files, 03/12/1965 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] No.41 3/12/65 Nation, Iselin, Martin 'from Stout (Poverty Takeout); No.7 3/12/65 Biz, Thomas from Rowen (General Aniline); No.11 3/12/65 Nation from Roberts (White House Sit in); No.24 3/12/65 Nation, Goldman, Kosner from Carter; (White House Sit In) Congress Week (foreign aid) Congress and Selma Situation; No.27 3/12/65 Mary Doris (for Christopher) from Kennedy (Wash.Bur.)
  - Chronological files, 03/13/1965-03/16/1965 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] Washington Index (March 15-20, 1965); No.5 (3/16/65) Brink from Gray (Ice-Pennsy); No.3 (3/16/65) Query Desk from Washington/Bradlee (Washington Bureau Schedule)
  - Chronological files, 03/17/1965 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid] Correction No.5 (3/17/65) from General Thomas D.; White No.8 3/17/65 Science, Hubbard from Simmons (Gemini Briefing); No.9 3/17/65 Newsmakers from Shaffer (Lausche); No.14 3/17/65 Nation from Roberts (LBJ Speech); No.17 3/17/65 Religion (Woodward) from Milligan Rev. William Baxter; No. 11 3/17/65 Elliot, Von Wettburg, Bernstein from Lippmann (Walter Lippmann on Europe Deserted?)
  - Chronological files, 03/18/1965 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    [from original finding aid] No.7 to Christopher from Weintal (Vietnam-Diplomatic); No.20 3/18/65 to Christopher from Weintal (Carrot and Stick); No.46 3/19/65 to Foreign from WEINTAL (German Statistical yearbook); No.14 to Christopher from Weintal (Soekarno); No.28 3/18/65 Nation (Kosner) from Just (Civil Rights); No.56 nation (Kosner) from Just (Civil Rights); No.20 3/17/65 Nation (Iselin) from Just(Justice Department type); No.l 3/17/65 Nation (Goldman) from Just (Reur Twelve); No.4 3/20/65 Nation from Just (Alabama Guardsmen)
  - Chronological files, 03/19/1965 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    [from original finding aid] Add to Congress and Civil Rights file; Congress and Civil Rights; Newsmakers from Shaffer (Ellender--); Newsmakers from Shaffer (Kennedy); Newsmakers from Shaffer (Senator Lausche said:); Newsmakers from Shaffer (Lausche); No.38 3/19/65 Nation, Sanders from Stout (Poor); No.3 31/17/65 Nation, Sanders from Stout (Poor); No.20 3/16/65 Nation, Iselin, Sanders from Stout(Poverty); No.2 31/8/65 Nation, Sanders, Iselin from Stout (Add Poor); No.17 3/18/65 to Nation, Sanders, Iselin from Stout(Add Poor)(Viste); No.49 3/19/65 Nation, Sanders from Stout (Add Poor); No.6 Nation, Iselin, Sanders from Stout (Add Poor); No.10 3/18/65 Photo, Orr from Stout (Poor); No.8 3/18/65 Nation,Sanders, Iselin from Stout(Add Poor); No.12 3/17/65 Photo, Orr from Stout (Poor); No.13 3/17/65 Nation, Sanders Iselin from Stout (Poor); No.7 3/19/65 Martz from Rowen (Excise Tax Cuts); No.28 3/19/65 Brink from Rowen (Wirtz); No.15 31/6/65 Biz " Rowen (Economy); No.13 Iselin Rowen--3/20/65 (Fowler); Correction No.11 3/20/65 Biz, Mintz and copy desk; from Rowen (T.rends) (Payments Bloc); No.18 3/17/65 Business, Brink from Rowen (Economy); No.40.3/19/65 Iselin from Rowen (Add Fowler); No. 18 3/18/65 Biz Brink from Rowen (1st take -Saxon, Silverthorne, Banks etc.); No.35 3/19/65 Business Trends Brink from Rowen
  - Chronological files, 03/19/1965 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    [from original finding aid] No.13 Press from Norman (3-19-65)(Censor); No.7 (3/20/65) Nation from Norman (Add Selma); No.l (3/18/65) Press from Norman (Censorship Query); No.3 (3/20/65) Nation from Norman (Selma); No.4 (3/16/65) Nation from Norman (Reserve-Army); No.2 (3/16/65) Foreign from Norman (Viet Cong Query); No.21 (3/18/65) Foreign /Nation/Periscope from Norman (Adm. McDonald on Vietnam); No.45 (3/19/65) Nation from Norman (Alabama Guard); No.2 (3/17/65) Foreign/Periscope from Norman(V ietnam) No.10 (3/17/65) Foreign from Norman (Vietnam); No.3 (3/19/65) Business from Norman (Defense Industry Forecasts); No.51 (3/19/65) Press from Norman (Add Censor); No.17 (3/16/65) Periscope/Foreign from Norman (Pentagon); TV No.32 Nation, Iselin from Lindsay (Voting Rights); No.15 (3/18/65) Nation, Iselin from Lindsay (5-Voting Rights Hearings); No.52 (3/19/65) Nation, Iselin from Lindsay (D.B.Hardeman); No.12 Religion, Woodward from Carter (Church and Race); No.11 Religion, Woodward from Carter (Church Cover); No.43 Clark, Medicine from Carter (White House Psychotics); No.19 (3/18/65) Nation, Goldman, Iselin, Elliott, Periscope from Carter (The Next Selma); No.18 Nation, Iselin, Goldman, Elliott from Carter (Bogalusa,La); No.4 (3/17/65) Nation, Religion from Carter (D.C. Demonstrations); No.5 (3/19/65) Von Wettberg from Crawford (LBJ under pressure); Correction no.6 Von Wettberg from Crawford; Correction no.10 Von Wettberg from Crawford
  - Chronological files, 003/20/1965-03/31/1965 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    [from original finding aid] Correction no.8 Foreign and Copy Desk from; Volkov-3/20/65 (Int 22 Soviet); No.19 Christopher from Volkov (Differences between B and K); No.14 (3/18/65) Foreign from Volkov (Leadall); Correction No.42 (3/19/65) Foreign and Copy Desk from Volkov (Rumania); No.39 (3/19/65) Foreign from Volkov (Rumania); No.14 (3/20/65) Latam, Christopher, Pearson from Van Voorst (Argentina: Vote); No.4 (3/18/65) Latam, Christopher, Pearson from Van Voorst (Haiti, Papa Doc Updater); No.37 (3/19/65) Foreign, Christopher, Martin from Van Voorst (Cyprus: Turkish Views); No.20 Foreign Christopher, Martin from Van Voorst(Cyprus: the week that was); No.25 (3/18/65) Latam, Christopher, Pearson from Van Voorst (Latam Conference); No.9 (3/19/65) Latam, Christopher, Pearson from Van Voorst (Argentina, March Elections); Ribicoff query (3/25/65) Bob Kennedy query (3/25/65) Congress and Civil Rights (3/26/65) Congressional reaction on Vietnam gas (3/25)
  - Chronological files, 04/1965 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    [from original finding aid] Correction (4/3/65)(N21 Violin); Civil Rights Subversion; Transition from Shaffer (Sinnott); Maxwell Taylor on Capitol Hill (4/2/65); Congress and Civil Rights; Congress and Vietnam; Congress Week; Correction (4/10/65) (N22 Congress); Correction (4/10/65)(N18 Violin); Congress Week (4/5/65); Newsmakers (roeder) from Shaffer (4/16)(page boy; salaries); Newsmakers from Shaffer (page boys) Bradford query (4/14/65); Civil Rights Debate Opens Letters (Wharton) from Shaffer (4/23/65)(The Orville Freeman Letter); Daylight Saving Time Legislation Civil Rights (Congress Week)-4/30/65; Congress and foreign policy 5/7/65 Foreign from Shaffer (your no.l of 5/6/65)(Robert Kennedy)
  - Chronological files, 05/01/1965-05/21/1965 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] New York Mayoralty race (5/13/65) Add to Dominican file; Ted Kennedy and the poll tax (the voting rights bill debate); No.l (5/17/65) Press from Just (Buchwald-Take One) No.2 (5/17/65) Press, Poll, from Just (Buchwald-Take Two); No.3 (5/17/65) Press, Pollak from Just (Buchwald-; Take Three) Correction No.18 (5/22/65) Press and Copy Desk from; Just (Buchwald); No.6 (5/20/65) Press, Pollak from Just (Buchwald) No.12 (5/18/65) Press, Pollak from Just (Buchwald-Take Four); Add to Excise Tax File (5/20/65); Business from Shaffer (Repeal of Taft-Hartley Act) Voting Rights Bill (5/20/65) Add on excise tax file (5/21/65); No.14 Nation--Greene from Russin (Chicago Mob) Nation Greene from Russin (Chicago Mob); Business (Martz) from Shaffer (excise tax )
  - Chronological files, 05/24/1965-05/27/1965 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] Washington Index May 24-29, 1965; No.2 5/22/65 Query Desk from Washington/Bradlee Correction; No.2 5/29/65 Iselin, Nation, Bernstein, Elliot, Lanser and Copy Desk from Bradlee (Nll-VDA);; No.21 5/26/65 Newsmakers, Roeder from Bradlee (Jim McShane); No. 22 5/26/65 Elliot, Lansner,Bernstein from Bradlee (Bridge Cheating); No. 17 5/26/65 Sports, Elliot, Lansner, Bernstein, Diamond, Christopher from Bradlee (Bridge Cheating); No.18 5/27/65 Diamond, Sports from Bradlee (Fight); No. 17 5/27/65 Diamond from Bradlee (Jan Becker Piece); No. 32 5/27/65 Christopher, guery desk, Latam from Bradlee (Stout); No.2 5/28/65 Diamond, Hubbard from Bradlee (Gemini Shot); No.16 5/27/65 Elliot, Lansner, Bernstein, Latam, Christopher, Iselin from Bradlee (Bundy); No.3 5/29/65 Christopher, Foreign, Latam, Elliott, Lansner, Bernstein from Bradlee (Dominica); No. 13 5/29/65 Latam, Library, Foreign from Bradlee (Bundy); No. 5 5/24/65 Press, Elliot, Lansner, Bernstein, Diamond Pollak from Bradlee (Buchwald's Special Column); No.4 5/29/65 Diamond, Pollak from Bradlee (Buchwald's story); No.30 5/29/65 Iselin, Nation from Bradlee (Kuchel); No.5 5/25/65 Diamond Life and Leisure from Bradlee (Hurley, Wisconsin); No.21 5/28/65 Iselin, Nation Bernstein from Bradlee (Rowan and the VOA); No.24 5/28/65 Iselin, Nation from Bradlee (VOA); No.l 5/27/65 Christopher from Bradlee (Fortas); No.18 5/26/65 Elliott, Lansner, Bernstein from Bradlee (Bridge Cheating); No.7 5/26/65 Newsmakers, Roeder from Bradlee (Jim McShane); No.6 5/26/65 Christopher from Bradlee (Bundy); No.5 5/26/65 Pollak from Bradlee (Buchwald); No.l 5/24/65 Pollak, Diamond, Lansner from Bradlee (Buchwald); No.2 5/24/65 Conway, Elliott, Lansner, Bernstein from Bradlee (Buchwald); No.3 5/24/65 Elliott, Lansner, Bernstein, Diamond from Bradlee (Buchwald); No.4 5/25/65 Brink, Lansner, Bernstein from Bradlee (100th US trade fair); No.7 5/25/65 Photo, Feeney from Norman (Reconnaissance photos and Russian Sam Missile Photos); No.9 5/26/65 Transition, Roeder from Norman (Halcomb); No.3 5/28/65 Foreign/Periscope from Norman (Monsoon campaign and "coup"); No.20 5/26/65 Foreign/Francois Sully from Norman (Map); No.8 5/25/65 Foreign/Nation from Norman (War Insert) No. 31 5/27/65 Foreign from Norman (Monsoon; No.6 (5/27/65 Foreign/Peri from Norman(Phony Coup/ Col.Thao) Correction; No.8 (5/29/65) Foreign and Copy Desk from Norman (Correction Int 18 Viet); No.3 (5/25/65) Foreign/Nation/Elliott/Lansner/from Norman (War); No. 3 (5/26/65) Nation/Foreign/Periscope/Elliott/Lansner Bernstein from Norman (McNamara Backgrounder); No. 3 (5/27/65) Nation/Foreign/Periscope/Elliott/Bernstein from Norman (McNamara and Davy Crockett); No. 11 (5/29/65) Nation/Foreign from Norman (McNamara and Vance Advisory); No. 27 5/28/65 Iiatam from Norman (Dominican Query); No. 11 Photo/ Kenney from Simmons (Gemini Suit Fix) (5/26/65); No. 23 (5/28/65) Photo, Jim Kenney from Simmons (Voskhod Interiors); No. 10 Science, Hubbard from Simmons (Gemini Extra-; No. 26 5/2-7/65 Science, Hubbard from Simmons (Gemini-4); No. 8 5/26/65 Education, Elfin from Simmons (commencement speeches); No.l 5/26/65 Photo (Whelan) from Milligan (Kuchel); No.2 5/26/65 Photo (Kenney) from Milligan (Brookings); No.39 5/27/65 Business (Barry) from Milligan (Wine Spotlight); No.28 5/27/65 Business (Barry) from Milligan (Wine Spotlight); No.14 5/26/65 Photo (Whelan) from Milligan (Voting Rights Bill); No.12 5/27/65 Photo, Feeney from Milligan (Martin); No.8 5/27/65 Photo, Feeney from Milligan (Martin); No.22 5/27/65 Photo (Kenney) from Milligan (air and water pollution); No.36 5/27/65 Newsmakers (Roeder) from Milligan(Emma Guffey Miller); No.12 5/26/65 Newsmakers from Milligan (Drew Pearson's comments); No.19 5/26/65 Business (Barry) from Milligan (Wine Industry Spotlight Query); No.25 (5/27/65) Foreign, Christopher from Volkov (Yugoslavs); No.13 (5/27/65) Nation from Volkov (Add VOA); No.16 (5/26/65) Nation from Volkov (Voice of America); No.29 5/28/65 Nation, Iselin from Volkov (Bradlee's memo on Rowan); No.18 5/28/65 Foreign, Christopher, Elliott, Lansner, Bernstein from Volkov (Kill #11); No.28 5/28/65 Foreign, Christopher from Volkov (Add Russia in Vietnam); No.9 Newsmakers from Volkov (K's Suit)(5-27-65); No.19 5/27/65 Von Wettberg and Copy Desk from Crawford Washington The Cool of Consensus; No.24 5/27/65 Leisure, Bernstein, Lansner, Elliott,Diamond from Russin (Story suggestion for Education Leisure, or Business); No.9 Nation, Iselin from Russin (poor Vote); No.15 5/28/65 Nation-Greene from Russin (Shriver Speech (with poor vote); No.38 5/27/65 Newsmakers, Roeder from Russin (Savio Marriage); No.5 5/27/68 Waters, Diamond, Iselin from Sanders (Beauty)
  - Chronological files, 05/28/1965 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Brink from Rowen (Abel); No.12 5/29/65 Education Elfin from Rowen (Brookings) Correction No.2 Education Elfin from Rowen (Brookings); No.14 5/28/65 Business Trends (Brink) from Rowen (Biz Trends); No.17 Brink from Rowen (Fowler Speech) (5-27-65); No.23 5/27/65 Biz,Brink, Landau from Rowen (Ackley and Fowler); No.9 5/29/65 Elfin from Rowen (Brookings); No.10 5/26/65 Biz, Brink, Morgello from Rowen(Economy Cover); No.4 5/24/65 Elfin from Rowen (Brookings) Correction; No.l 5/29/65 Business Trends and Copy Desk from Rowen (Biz Trends); No.6 5/25/65 Brink and Morgello from Rowen (Economy Cover); No.7 Periscope, Nation, Foreign, Latam (5-28-65) from Weintal (Dominican Republic) Correction; No.6 5/29/65 Foreign and Copy Desk from Weintal (Int 17 Leadall); No.2 5/27/65 Christopher from Weintal (Soviets); No.10 5/29/65 Foreign (Christopher) from Weintal (Collier Story); No.5 Christopher from Weintal (Whither Europe?)(EFTA Meeting); No.19 5/28/65 Christopher from Weintal (your query #5)(Martin Piece); No.22 5/28/65 Biz/Brink from Gray (Pay GS14); No.15 5/27/65 Photo/Whelan from Gray (Vince Finnigan Assignment; communist mail); No.20 5/27/65 Diamond/Leisure/Waters from Gray (Side walk Cafes); No.35 5/27/65 Nation/Iselin from Gray (Harry Byrd); No.33 5/27/65 Nation/Goldman from Gray (Communist mail); No.14 5/27/65 Nation/ Iselin from Gray (Harry Byrd)1 5/28/65 Foreign, Christopher, Martin from Lindsay (Add Latam); No.12 5/28/65 Foreign, Christopher, Martin from Lindsay(Add Latam); No.20 5/28/65 Foreign, Christopher, Martin from Lindsay(Add Latam); No.21 5/27/65 Foreign, Christopher, Martin from Lindsay (Latam); No.11 Foreign, Christopher from Lindsay (Latin America); No.26 5/28/65 Newsmakers, Roeder from Lindsay (Powell) Newsmakers/Nation from Shaffer (Margaret Chase Smith) Newsmakers (Roeder) from Shaffer (Humphrey query)(5/28/65) Nation from Shaffer Voting Rights (5/28/65)
  - Chronological files, 05/29/1965-05/30/1965 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Correction Periscope and Copy Desk from Shaffer-5/29/65 (Item 18 Thurmond the Invincible) Correction No.14 5/29/65 Latam and Copy Desk from Stout (Amer 11); No. 5 5/29/65 Latam from Stout (DR) Correction; No.7 5/29/65 Periscope and Copy Desk from Shaffer (Item 18 Thurmond the Invincible); No.25 5/28/65 Newsmakers/Nation from Shaffer(Margaret Chase Smith); No.8 Newsmakers (Roeder) from Shaffer (Humphrey Query)(5-28-56); No.29 5/27/65 Nation from Shaffer (Voting Rights)
  - Chronological files, 06/1965 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Congress Week (6/4/65); Add to Congress file (Shriver matter); Martz (Biz) from Shaffer (6-10)(Excise Taxes); Newsmakers from Shaffer (6-10)(Bob Kennedy); Congress Week (6/14/65); The Lyndon Johnson Style; Congress Week; Add to Congress Week-June 18,1965; Add to Congress and Vietnam file (6/18/65); Congress and Vietnam (6/18/65); Congress Week (6/25/65); Bob Kennedy (6/25/65) (raft trip query); Bob Kennedy (6/25/65); Alice in Wonderland Query; Coleman (6/25/65); Congress Week (6/30/65)
  - Chronological files, 07/1965 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Query No.13 of 7/6/65; Congress Week (7/965); Morgan tailpiece nine July 1965; Johnson Cover (7/12/65); Religion from Shaffer (Mormon query (7/14/65)); Biz trends from Shaffer (Eastern Airlines); Congress Week (7/6/65); Coleman (7/6/65); Vietnam (7/16/65); Newsmakers, Roeder from Shaffer July 21, 1965 (Senate); Henry Hazlett from Shaffer 7/22/65; Telephonic request on certain LBJ anecdotes (7/22/65); Congress Week (7/23/65); Correction (7/24/65)(N17 Congress); Biz/Barry from Shaffer, Washington July 27, 1965; (Fulbright Speech) Biz/Barry, Brink from Shaffer, Washington July 27,1965; (Firestone); LBJ and Vietnam (for the violin)(7/30/65) Congress Week (7/30/65)
  - Chronological files, 08/1965-09/1965 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] Congress Week (9/10/65); Correction (9/11/65)(N25 New Congress); Newsmakers from Shaffer (9/8)(Carl Leubsdorf); Military aid-- the congressional concern (9/16/65); Fulbright and Dominican speech; Congress Week (9/17/65); Correction (9/18/65)(N17 Fulbright); Congress Week (9/12/65); Nation and Photo (Orr)from Shaffer--9/23/65; (Senator Ernest Gruening) 14(b)(9/26/85) Medicine from Shaffer (September 29, 1965); (Hart's Statement) Morrissey Nomination; Nation--Iselin from - Shaffer (Morrissey) Home Rule (B.C.)
  - Chronological files, 10/1965 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid] Home Rule (B.C.); Wallace; Correction (N12 Morrissey); Victor Borge ceremony; GI Bill (10/6/65); SEC Probe; Congress (146); Wade Nomination; 14B-latest development (10/8/65); (Response to telephone request ) (October 13, 1965); Query #2; Morrissey (10/14/65); 14 (b) -- 10/14/65; Kuchel (10/16/65); Correction ( 10/16/65) (N16 New Morrissey); Advisory on GOP races; The Fabulous Congress (10-19); Morrissey (10/21/65); Mel from Sam (info, from Vice President's office); New faces in Congress; Resignation of the Admirals (October 28, 1965); Neuberger (10/30/1965); Iselin from Shaffer (endorsing Beame); Diamond, Press from Shaffer (Tom McIntyre); Correction (10/30/65) (N12 Congress)
  - Chronological files, 11/1965-12/1965 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    [from original finding aid] Cover Story ( 11/4/65) (Election Returns); Udall (5/11/65); Urban Affairs (1Q/10/65); Byrd (10/11/65); Religion, Woodward from Shaffer (Jewish Fund Raising); Correction (N-13 Congress Travel) (Rep. John J.Rooney); #1 Washington from Nation (Percy); Your query fl 12/1/65 (Paul Douglas); No. 8 of Nov. 30 - (Bob Kennedy); Junkets; Democratic program book; Query t2 on Mecom (12/8/65); Democratic money-raising; Discount Rate (12/8/65); #3 Washington from Business (Martz ) (Discount Rate); The Post editorial, "Political Medicine" (December 16,1965); Violin (12/21/65) (Second session of 89th Congress) Fulbright (12-22); Saltonstall (supplementing other material) 12/30/1965
  - Chronological files, 01/01/1966-01/12/1966 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Peace Offensive in Congress; Nation=Iselin, Goldman from Shaffer (telephonic; suggestion) Cover Story; Add to Kennedy Cover File (January 5, 1965) Nation (Iselin) Goldman from Shaffer (White House; Meeting (1-6-66); Correction (1/8/66)(Nil Congress) 14(b); Correction (Nil Gavin) and (N12 Hearings) Vietnam/Congress (1/10/66)
  - Chronological files, 01/13/1961-01/31/1966 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] Violin (State of Union message)-1/13/65; Query #3 1/14/65 (Vietnam War); Vietnam Debate in Congress (1/14/65); GOP State of Union Address plus Congress Week (1/20/66); Violin (1.27.66); 14(b)
  - Chronological files, 02/1966 (Box 20, Folder 3)